Being bad never looked so good!
Bandidas is a action, comedy, western film directed by Joachim Rønning.
When a ruthless robber baron takes away everything they cherish, a rough-and-tumble, idealistic peasant
and a sophisticated heiress embark on a quest for justice, vengeance…and a few good heists.
Maria Alvarez, played by Penélope Cruz.
Sara Sandoval, played by Salma Hayek Pinault.
Quentin, played by Steve Zahn.
Tyler Jackson, played by Dwight Yoakam.
Ashe, played by Denis Arndt.
Bill Buck, played by Sam Shepard.
Bandidas is a 2006 Western action comedy film directed by Norwegian directors Joachim Rønning and Espen
Sandberg, in their feature directorial debut, and produced and co-written by Luc Besson.
Starring Salma Hayek and Penélope Cruz, it tells the tale of two very different women in late-19th-century Mexico
who become a bank robbing duo in an effort to combat a ruthless enforcer terrorizing their town.
This is the first film that Cruz and Hayek starred in together.
It was an international co-production between
France, the United States and Mexico.
Filming took place in Sierra de Órganos National Park in the town of Sombrerete,
Mexico, as well as in the Mexican states of Durango and San Luis Potosí.
Released on February 3, 2006, it received mixed reviews from critics.
The film explores themes of mexico, bank robber,
revenge, best friend, bank robbery.
The tone is lighthearted.